Yorman Felipe Rivero

Software Engineer

3:

Location: San Cristobal, Tachira, Venezuela

Phone: 0584247202001

Email: felipe.riverot@gmail.com

Web/portfolio:

https://feliperivero99.github.io

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/feliperivero99/



Software Engineer, Web developer specializing in front end development. Experienced with app and desktop development. Experienced mainly as web developer using Wordpress and Ruby on Rails, working in all the stages of development cycle for Dynamic web projects. Experienced in app development using Phonegap and Cordova. Finally, I worked as Data scientist using Python for data análisis and R for data visualizations.

EDUCATION

2018 Degree: Ingenierio en Informatica (Software Engineer)
San Cristobal - Venezuela
Universidad Nacional Experimental del Tachira

Languages: Spanish: Native

English: Advanced German: Basic French: Basic

Skills: Wordpress, Laravel, Ruby On rails, Python, Java (with the IDE Netbeans and eclipse), CCS, Javascript (Jquery and libraries), PHP, Phpmyadmin, Bootstrap 4, Git, AWS services (s3, Route 53, EC2, api Gateway,

DynamoDB), C/C++, R

WORK EXPERIENCE

2012 - 2015 ERPcontable - Desktop Development and Web Development

San Cristobal, Venezuela Position: Junior developer

Responsibilities: Lead developer of CRM module. Second developr of ERP software.

> Customer support Web Developer

2015 - 2016 Can Polit - Web Developer

San Cristobal, Venezuela Position: Web Developer

Responsibilities: Web Developer with Ruby On Rails Bootstrap Designer.

2016 -2018 Agropezim - Web Development / Data Analytics

San Cristobal, Venezuela Position: Web Developer – data scientist

Responsibilities: Web developer using Wordpress

App developer using Cordova/Phonegap

Web and server administrator.

AWS Administrator

Data analysis using Python and R

Jan/2019 - Sept/2019 Shokworks / 2waysports - Web Development and infrastructure

San Cristobal, Venezuela Position: Web Developer - infrastructure

Responsibilities: Web developer using Wordpress Web and server administrator. AWS Administrator

Sept/2019 Itzonecl - Web Development

San Cristobal, Venezuela Position: Web Developer - infrastructure

Responsibilities: Web developer using Wordpress Web developer using Laravel

PROJECTS

2018 Possible (finalizando)

Made with: html, ccs y javascript

URL: http://possiblecr.com.mocha3023.mochahost.com/



Nuestras Servicios

¡Invierte de manera inteligente y busca asesoramiento profesional! Costa Rica es considerado uno de los mejores países Latinoamericanos para invertir.

2018 El Universo del tarot

Made with Wordpress, css, jquery, javascript.

Plugins: Woocommerce, Avchat (servicio de videochat), Polylang, divi theme, etc

URL: https://eluniversodeltarot.com/



Somos una comunidad tarotistas profesionales, queremos darte las respuestas que necesitas a todos tus problemas, conecta con nosotros y las cartas del tarot. Es muy sencillo, paga tu paquete de respuestas a través de email, haz las preguntas y tendrás las respuestas del tarot en tu bandeja de correo electrónico.

Tarotistas



2017 Rentadvisor (inactive)

Made With Wordpress, css, jquery, javascript.



2017 Agropezim

Made With html, css, jquery, javascript.



PERSONAL REFERENCES

Madelyn Alejandra Castillo Software Engineer

Phone: 584143791689 E-mail: madalecastillo@gmail.com

Crysler Enoc belisario Software Engineer

Phone: 584247413404 E-mail: cyrenoc@gmail.com

Esneldy Yelireth Caballero Software Engineer

Phone: 584164769429 E-mail: esneldyc.09@gmail.com

COURSES

- 5to Congreso Internacional de Tecnología Web, Informática & E-Business 2009. (International Congress about Web technologies and E-bussiness)
- ICATEC, Introduction to english, 24 hours.
- Universidad Católica del Táchira, Basic English, 60 hours.
- Universidad Católica del Táchira, English level 1, 60 hours.
- Coursera, Human Computer Interaction, 90 hours.
- Coursera, Machine Learning Python, 90 hours.
- Coursera, R Programming, 90 hours.
- Coursera, Python Introduction, 90 hours.
- Coursera, Python For Everybody, 90 hours.
- Coursera, Python Data Structures, 90 hours.
- Coursera, Data Scientist Toolbox, 60 hours.

Spor Hobbies: Tennis, aikido, fitness, hiking, mountaineering.